－＝多米诺字幕组 倾情奉献＝－
本字幕仅供学习交流之用 严禁用于商业用途
摩根学校
弗莱迪・海默
艾玛・罗伯茨
家庭作业
翻译 Winter
翻译 意境啊意境
翻译 白色线
翻译 蒙洛奇
校对 蒙洛奇
校对 西西
校对 Winter
后期 艾迪爱慕
利他林(中枢兴奋药)   立普能(抗忧郁药)
告诉我 你为什么不结婚
我还没邂逅我的梦中女孩
你喜欢我么
当然不
人才招聘会
新年快乐
Zoe她家
哥伦布6酒店
二十层见
驱逐令
情人节餐单
我想见你
? I've got a cupboard with cans of food ?
? Filtered water and pictures of you ?
? And I'm not coming out until this is all over ?
? And I'm looking through the glass ?
? Where the light bends at the cracks?
? And I'm screaming at the top of my lungs ?
? Pretending the echoes belong to someone ?
? Someone I used to know ?
? And we become ?
? Silhouettes when our bodies finally go ?
从人类历史有记录开始
Since the dawn of recorded history,
大约有1100亿人
something like 110 billion
在这个世界上出生
human beings have been born into this world.
这数字靠单一的个体是不可能完成的
And not a single one of them made it.
在这个星球上住着68亿人
There are 6.8 billion people on the planet.
每年大概有6000万人去世  6000万人
Roughly 60 million of them die every year. 60 million people.
这就可以得出结论 每天有16万人去世
That comes out to about 160,000 per day.
我小时候读到这么一句话
I read this quote once when I was a kid,
"我们孤单地活着 终将孤单地死去
"We live alone, we die alone.
人生不过一场虚无"
Everything else is just an illusion. "
这话曾让我想到半夜睡不着觉
It used to keep me up at night.
我们都孤单地活着
We all die alone.
那我为什么要
So, why am I supposed to
操劳 艰苦还有挣扎
spend my life working, sweating, struggling?
当那一切都不过是一场虚无
For an illusion?
即使有再多的朋友
Because no amount of friends,
再多的女友
no girl,
再多的满分作业
no assignments about conjugating the pluperfect
或者算出直角三角形斜边的平方根
or determining the square root of the hypotenuse
都不能避免我最终离世的命运
is gonna help me avoid my fate.
我的生活应当做更有意义的事
I have better things to do with my time.
George 作业做完了吗
Do you have your work, George?
- 没  - 为什么
- No. - Why not?
因为我有点沮丧
I was depressed.
是嘛 怎么回事
Oh, yes? Why was that?
因为我意识到我终有一天会死去
Because I realized I'm gonna die one day.
George 我们都会离开人世
We're all gonna die one day, George.
我想 这不是你不做三角函数作业
I don't think that's a reasonable excuse
的合理解释
for not completing your trigonometry exercise.
我逼迫自己去做了
Well, I was trying to.
但我终将死去的事实在我脑海中不断萦绕
I just couldn't shake this awareness of my mortality.
世事都变得没有意义
Everything seemed meaningless,
很不幸 写作业也包括在内
including the assignment, unfortunately.
你给我去校长办公室
I want you to go to the principal's office
去发现写作业的意义
and find meaning in the homework.
并且在期末前把作业交给我
Bring it to me completed by the end of the period.
- 你迟到了  - 我写作业太专心了
- You're late. - I was so engrossed in my work.
孩子 你又要挨训了
Boy, I wouldn't wanna be you right now.
- 我什么也没做  - 你总是做错事
- I haven't done anything. - You've always done something.
你最好快点去
You better go.
Bill.
虽然你是毕业生 有校外活动的特权
Even though you have off-campus privileges as a senior,
如果你被发现在校外吸烟的话
if you are seen anywhere in the city smoking,
你的特权将被撤回 即时生效
you have your privileges revoked. Automatic probation.
干嘛告诉我这些
Why are you telling me?
- 你以为我闻不出来吗  - 随便你
- You think I can't smell? - You can smell all you want.
我们能进入正题了吗
Shall we get down to business?
那么开始吧
Yes, we shall.
从某种层面说 你的未来决定于接下来几个月的表现
In a way, your future depends on the next few months.
不只是为了上大学
Not just for college.
而是为你的将来打下基础
I mean, it sets the tone for everything that follows.
我知道你是怎么想的
Now, I know how you think and I know
你认为现在太晚了 而你又是宿命论者
you're thinking it's too late and you're gonna be a fatalist
对现在的一切毫不在乎
and let it all go to hell.
但是 George 如果你坚持你现在所走的路
But, George, if you keep performing the way you are,
就别想毕业了 更别说上大学了
forget about college, forget about graduating, even.
所以
So,
这次只是处以警告 再有下次就是开除学籍了
this counts as your official warning. Suspension is next.
下次应该是留校察看吧
I thought probation was next.
别威胁我 这不管用
Don't play the angles, George. They won't work.
也别开玩笑
Neither do jokes.
我没开玩笑
I wasn't joking.
我知道你很有才华
I know you're capable.
我积极性方面真的很成问题
I have a real problem with motivating.
但我想我会设法克服
But I think I can do it.
我会努力的
I'll try.
好吧 可以出去了
All right, go.
不要让我失望了
And don't make me regret it.
谁在天台上吸烟
Who's smoking up here?
George 你知道你在干什么吗
George! What do you think you're doing?
对不起 我
Sorry. I...
我今天真的很不顺
I was having a tough day.
我承受的压力很大 Dougherty夫人
I guess the stress finally got to me, Mrs. Dougherty.
George 为什么要吸烟
George, why do you do these things?
谢谢你
Thank you.
什么压力
Now, what do you mean by stress?
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
- 我收到了你学校发来的邮件  - 天哪
- I got an e-mail from your school. - Oh, Jesus.
类似于留校察看
Some kind of academic probation?
我能帮你吗
Can I help you?
要不请个家庭教师或者私立大学的导师
Can I get you a tutor or a private college advisor?
如果你考不进一个像样的学校
If you don't get into a decent school,
我都不知道你能不能找到工作了
then I don't know how you're gonna get a job.
我自己能处理
I have it under control.
亲爱的 如果你考不进一个像样的大学
Honey, if you don't get into a decent college...
- 我看电视去了  - 不准去
- I'm gonna go watch TV. - No, you will not watch TV.
呆在这
You will stay here
直到我们想出切实可行的方案
till we can come up with a plan for getting you into college.
我今天在学校过得很不顺 我很累了
I had a hard day at school, I'm tired,
我现在想要休息半个小时
and I'm gonna go relax now for half an hour.
然后我就去做作业 可以吗
Then I will do my work. Okay?
George?
TMD你在干什么
The fuck are you doing?
画画
I'm drawing.
你这臭小子 找到素描素材了没
Are you sketching your subject, you little shit?
是的
Yes.
- Harris 我没有素材 - 见鬼 为什么没有
- I don't have a subject, Harris. - Why the heck not?
不知道
I don't know.
George 你要善于发掘身边的事物
George, you're going to have to start digging around in there,
那样才能开发自身的潜能
so you can develop that talent of yours,
才能有想法
so you can start to use that brain of yours
去表达内心深处的美丽
to express that beautiful heart of yours.
好好想想你要传达的是什么 然后画出来
So, figure out what you want to say, and say it.
- Harris  - 嗯
- Harris. - Yes.
我没有什么要传达的
I don't have anything to say.
用心去找
Find something!
- 嘿 - 嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
- 我是Sally  - 我知道
- I'm Sally. - I know.
谢谢你替我顶罪
Thanks for covering for me.
不用谢
No problem.
为什么那么做
Why did you?
不知道
I don't know.
你特立独行
You were doing something so renegade,
不该因教条受到惩罚
I thought you deserved to get away with it.
我三天两头被叫到办公室
I run afoul of the authorities so often,
处理这样的事比你有经验
I figured I could handle it better than you.
你真的很怪
You're really weird.
为什么一直不写作业
So, why don't you ever do your work?
有那么多比写作业更重要的事去做
There are so many more important things to think about,
于是写作业就可做可不做了
homework ends up seeming like an afterthought.
注意力不足过动症吗
Add?
不 他们做了所有的努力
No, they tried everything.
利他林 普能 导师 心理治疗
Ritalin, Lexapro, tutors, therapy.
不起作用的 我就像懒虫中的战斗机
Nothing worked. I'm the Teflon slacker.
其实我们每个人都在死去 你懂不
No, it's more like, we're living in a dying time, you know?
全球变暖 战争 恐怖行动还有海啸
I mean, you got global warming, wars, terrorism, tsunamis.
- 好了  - 我们整个社会正在走向衰落
- Okay... - We're definitely on the downhill side.
那我们努力活着为了什么 有什么用呢
So, what are we working towards? What's the point?
我也会恐惧 但是都没你那样的
I thought I had fears, but they're pretty run-of-the-mill.
- 我惧怕痛苦还有死亡  - 我不害怕这些
- Pain, death. - Not me.
我怕的是活着
I fear life.
George 你有朋友吗
Do you have any friends, George?
我有点愤世嫉俗
I'm kind of a misanthrope.
这不由我决定
Not a choice, just a fact.
再见 帅哥
Okay, handsome.
妈妈 注意形象
Mom! Jesus!
嗨 翘鼻子
Hi, banana!
进来吗
You wanna come up?
对于刚才的事很抱歉 我们度过了一个美好的夜晚
I'm sorry about that, chicken. We had a really late night.
你上学前我们刚到家
I think we got home right before you left for school.
妈妈 这是我新结识的朋友 George
Mom, this is my new friend, George.
- 你好 George  - 你好 Howe夫人
- Well, George. - Hello, Mrs. Howe.
- 见到你很高兴  - 很高兴
- What a genuine pleasure. - Very nice to...
Sally 高脚杯放哪了
Sally, do you know where our stemware went?
我想喝杯白兰地
I'm drinking wine out of a tumbler.
George 你喝什么
What do you want, George?
我们在乡下时就那么干
And this was before we left the sticks.
我使了一下颜色 向下看
So, I cock one eye, look down,
以为会看到一只田鳖
expecting to see a giant water bug,
或是水蛇 或是
or a water moccasin, or...
一些我巴不得杀了的水生动物
Water something. Something I had to kill.
但却是飞行员的手
But it was the pilot's hand!
别激动
Oh!
痒不痒 这里
Ticklish, this one!
拿条毛巾给你
Let me get you a paper towel.
你们知道吗 怕痒的人都是好情人
You know, ticklish people make great lovers.
身体的每一处都能唤起情欲
Everything is erogenous.
天哪 太神了
My God. She's amazing.
如果你是她女儿就不那么想了
Not if you're her daughter.
怎么来纽约了
How'd you end up in New York?
我母亲16岁的时候有了我 我父亲是一名卡车司机
My mom had me when she was 16. My dad was a truck driver,
有一天他离开了就再也没有回来过
and one day he took off and never came back.
那是在哪里
And this was?
克拉克斯堡 田纳西州的一个小镇
Clarksburg. It's a small town in Tennessee.
他是纽约的暴发户 有一家纺织厂
This rich guy from New York, who owned a textile plant,
他拯救了我们
started coming down, and it
就像是垂死之人抓到救命稻草
was like we were castaways and he was the ship.
但我是8岁时来这的
But I ended up here,
新学校 新朋友和漂亮的新衣服
eight years old, new school, new friends, fancy new clothes.
我妈妈一年前和他离婚了
My mom divorced him a year ago,
现在又恢复神经质的单身生活
and now she's back on the singles scene with a vengeance.
我该做作业去了
I do think I should get some homework done, though.
我也该回去了  有事要做
I should get going then. Got work to do myself.
不错
Yeah, right.
谢谢
Thank you.
再见
Goodbye.
这不是第一次发生了
It's not the first time it's happened.
我知道
I know.
你也从来不认为他们会发生这样的事
But you never think it's gonna be the people that it's gonna be.
他们都在一起15年了
They've been together for 15 years.
这当然很荒谬
I know. It's certainly ridiculous.
- 怎么没电了  - 嗨 亲爱的
- What happened to the electricity? - Hi, sweetie.
我们叫了烤鸡店的外卖
We got take-out from the rotisserie chicken place.
拿碟子来和我们一起吃吧
Grab a plate and join us.
为什么没电了 发生了什么
But the lights. What happened?
我的错 忘了付电费
It's my fault. I forgot to pay the bill.
没事 明天就有电了
And it's no big deal. They'll be on tomorrow.
George 我们可以将这
George, we're trying to turn
有点尴尬混乱的场面当作一次有趣的经历
this awkward little mix-up into a fun experience.
如果你不想加入我们的话
And if you can't get into the spirit of adventure,
可以做你自己的事
then you can just do your own thing.
也不必呆在这了
You don't have to stick around.
还真抱歉 Jack 我不能用手提电脑了
I'm sorry, Jack. I can't use my laptop,
更不用说写作业了
much less get my assignments.
可以去图书馆或者星巴克啊 要善于应变
So, go to the library or Starbucks. Be resourceful.
有人知道小说中的
Does anyone have any ideas about
哪些部分
which elements of the novel
具有文学浪漫主义运动的特征吗
pinpoint it as part of the Romantic movement?
有人知道吗
Anyone?
George?
是
Yeah?
我的问题是在我们做的作业中
I was asking what conclusion
你得出了什么结论
you came to in the exercise we're doing.
抱歉 能再说一遍吗
Sorry. About what, again?
小说中的那些部分
About which elements of the novel
具有文学浪漫主义运动的特征
pinpoint it as part of the Romantic movement?
哪部小说
Which novel?
《卡斯特桥市长》
The Mayor of Casterbridge,
George 很显然 你没读过
George, which, obviously, you didn't read.
我很喜欢这小说
I loved it.
看得出  还有人知道吗
Clearly. Anyone else?
这部小说中我最喜欢的
My favorite part of the
是室内商业区的布局
book is how the town's layout is described
以纵览整座城镇的
from the perspective of a bee
蜜蜂的视角来描述
traveling from one side of town to the other.
这样的描述很形象
It's so visual.
我认为Hardy采用自然界中
So, I guess what Hardy's doing is aligning his point of view
最小 最纤弱的昆虫的视角来描述
not with an all-seeing God but with an insect,
而不是全能全知的视角进行描述
the tiniest, humblest creature in nature.
这样的手法很有浪漫主义运动的特征
Which is pretty Romantic.
George 我想你找到学期论文的主题了
I think you just found your term paper, George.
George!
Hi.
- 和我们一起吧  - 好
- Come join us. - Cool.
你认识Will和Zoe吧
You know Will and Zoe, right?
我们一起上数学课
Yeah, we're in math class together, right?
你从没写过作业
You never have your homework.
对 这是我的特色
Right. Right, it's my shtick.
- 你好 George - 你好 Zoe
- Hi, George. - Hey, Zoe.
哥们 你总是在画些什么
Dude, what are you always drawing?
他就像是发狂的艺术家 整天弯腰驼背在书上画些什么
He's like the mad artist, just hunched over his books.
从不听老师讲课
He never listens to a word the teacher says.
- 你不也一样吗  - 我能看看你画的那堆狗屎吗
- What, like you do? - Can I see some of the shit you draw?
当然
Yeah, sure.
一整本呢
You have issues.
哥们 你感情很细腻
No. Dude, you're sensitive.
多愁善感的画师
The sensitive artiste.
能给我的派对画一幅这样的画吗
Could you draw something like this for one of my parties?
在我弟弟除夕夜派对上贴上一幅巨大的画
I'm throwing a huge one at my brother's club on New Year's Eve.
- 说真的  - 当然
- You serious? - Yeah.
可以把它放大 做海报 邀请贴之类的
You know, we can blow it up, make it a poster, invites, flyers.
很不错 不是吗
Yeah, that'd be great, right?
- 嘿 George 你好吗  - 我很好
- Hey, George. How are you? - Fine.
干什么呢
Well, what are you doing?
写三角函数作业
Just finishing my trig assignment.
好孩子 这是我喜欢听到的
Good man. That's what I like to hear.
我收到了72人的回复
I've got 72 comps on my list alone.
- 大多是你的朋友  - 嗯
- Most of them are your friends. - Yeah.
他们会是派对上最酷的
And they're gonna be the coolest people there.
- 没错  - 别怀疑
- Yeah, you're right. - So don't question it.
而且 如果我叫上我的人 你的整体运作都将瘫痪
Besides, if I pull my people, your whole operation goes under.
- Will  - George小弟
- Will. - Brother George!
伙计 我太喜欢了
I love it, man.
正合适派对
Nice celebratory mood. Perfect for a party.
下一步呢 巴斯奎特（著名艺术家）
So, what now, Basquiat?
守则第一条是翘课
Rule number one about cutting school.
我以前逃过课
I've cut school before.
去商店购物
To shop.
- 守则第一条 旷课很有趣  - 这什么守则
- Rule number one, cutting school is fun. - That's a rule?
守则第二条  少旷课以保持新鲜感
Rule number two, cut rarely to preserve the specialness.
这是话么
Is that even a word?
守则第三条
Rule number three,
买些书增加人文方面的修养
do something culturally
能促进道德的提升
rewarding with your time to earn it morally.
守则第四条 你是个呆子
Rule number four, you're a dork.
错 第四条是面条(双关:笨蛋)
Wrong. Rule number four, noodles.
面条
Noodles?
你就是那么看我们的
Is that how you see us?
你是个老人而我是你12岁的侄女
You're the old man and I'm your 12-year-old niece?
不是
No.
你带每个认识的女孩
So, what, you take all the
去看这部电影 这就是你秘密武器
girls to this movie? Is it your secret weapon?
玩什么不是玩
When you're cutting school, you go to whatever's playing.
我开玩笑的
I'm kidding.
- 等一下  - 干嘛
- Whoa. - What?
- 那是我继父  - 所以呢
- That's my stepfather. - So?
首先 他办公室在镇上的另一头
Well, A, his office is on the other side of town.
其次 他看上去很怪
And B, he looks weird.
我们跟踪他吧
Let's follow him.
你认为他在做什么
What do you think he's doing?
也许只是赶去开会
Probably just going to a meeting.
我打赌是和情人幽会
I bet it's a lovers' rendezvous.
我继父就一直那么干
My stepfather cheated all the time.
也许吧
Maybe.
无意冒犯 但是他看起来很吓人
No offense, but he looks kind of creepy.
开会才不会来这
Strange place for a meeting.
看来也不是什么
Lovers' rendezvous amended to
幽会地点了
drug buy from skanky hooker.
嘿 Bill
Hey, Bill.
你就像冷战时的间谍一样 来去无踪
You are like a Cold War spy. You move only in shadow.
我 我一直在附近啊
Me? I'm always around.
我看你交了些新朋友
I see you made some new friends.
不完全是
Not necessarily. Jury's still out.
我为你高兴 George 只是
I'm happy for you, George. I just...
我希望你小心点
I just want you to be careful.
- 他们怎么了  - 没啥
- What's wrong with them? - Nothing.
但是他们通过考试都比你容易
But they have an easier time of getting by than you do.
你跟不上这个学习团体的步伐
You're not exactly hooking up with a study group.
告诉你点消息
Hey, I have something for you.
几周后该开"职业介绍日"了
Career Day is coming up in a few weeks,
我们总是会让一名模范学生
and we always assign an exemplary student
代替摩根学校向同学发言
to represent Morgan to the alumni speakers.
就像联络员一样
You know, to act as a liaison,
陪同他们到教室 诸如此类
escort them to the classroom, whatever...
你真的是疯了
You have really lost it.
Dougherty夫人给我说了你那事儿
Then there is that matter that Mrs. Dougherty broached to me.
- 候选者  - 对
- The substitute? - Yeah.
在学校是抽烟是要开除学籍的
Smoking on campus is automatic suspension.
这是我最不想干的事
This is the last thing I wanna do.
没问题 开除学籍 就这样了
No problem. Suspension it is. Done. Effective...
好的 我去
Fine. Fine.
- 我会去的  - 很好 很好
- I'll do it. - Great. Great.
我们会把计划书
We'll be sending out an e-mail
和你的工作任务发邮件给你
with your schedule and your responsibilities.
你是Dustin吗
Are you Dustin?
对
Yeah.
我是George 我是你的联络员
Hi. I'm George. I'm your liaison.
你好
Hey.
我是Dustin Heath
My name is Dustin Heath.
我曾经是这里的学生
I'm a student. I was a student here.
我和那个可怕的老头儿在一个班
I was in the class with that terrifying old man over there.
我是艺术家
Yeah, I'm an artist.
说实话 我也不知道我在这里做什么
Honestly, I don't know what I'm doing here.
他们打电话邀请我来那会儿我宿醉还没醒呢
Was a little hungover when they called me and asked me to do this
我想快点挂电话然后就同意了
and I said yes just to get them off the phone.
几天后我就收到了计划书
I got the schedule in the mail several days later
然后我就有点尴尬
and I was a little embarrassed.
我没有什么成就
I'm not really established or anything.
一年前我第一次办艺术展 挺不错
I had my first art show a year ago, which was good.
买了这件外套
Got me this coat.
我给你们看一些我的作品吧
Well, let me show you some of my work here.
我不知道 有时人们认为你的作品
I don't know, sometimes people look at your stuff
他们认为很有趣
and, you know, they think it's really interesting
或者就是一坨狗屎
or they think it's bullshit,
我不知道两者的区别 确实不知
and I don't know the difference. I honestly don't.
我想 只要不欺骗自己就行 了
You just, you know, hope not to be fooling yourself, I guess.
这是下一张
This is the next slide, here.
你们有问题吗
Anybody have any questions?
没人问我问题 我刚是不是太差劲了
I mean, nobody asked me any questions. Did I just suck?
你是今天发言者中
You were probably the only real,
最真材实料 毫不浮夸的人
non-full-of-shit person speaking today.
就像原子弹轰过似的
It felt like Nagasaki in there.
你很棒
You were great.
谢谢 哥们
Thanks, man.
你也画画吗
Do you paint?
对 我喜欢画画
Yeah, I'd like to.
只是不知道画什么
I just don't know what to paint.
知道吗 这才是最艰难的
Yeah, well, it's the hardest part, you know?
这会让我成不了画家吗
Does that make me not a painter?
你所追求的事实才是作画的真谛
The fact that you struggle with it is a really good thing.
但你不作画又怎能自称画家
But how can you call yourself a painter if you don't paint?
- 你喜欢摩根学校么  - 不是很喜欢
- You like Morgan? - Not really.
我不知道在这干什么
I have no idea what I'm doing here.
我想没有人知道 George
I don't think anybody does, George.
至少你敢于承认
At least you admit it.
如果愿意 你可以来我
If you want, you can come to
布鲁克林的工作室 看一些作品
my studio in Brooklyn and check some stuff out.
你准备假期一直闲逛吗
You sticking around for the holidays?
不 去圣巴特岛 玩家庭游艇
Nah. St. Bart's. Family yacht.
这样
Oh.
开玩笑啦 没计划
Kidding. No plans.
你真杯具
You're a loser.
我也是 咱俩应该出去玩玩
Well, me, too. We should hang out.
也许吧
Maybe.
圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas!
- 你好 - 你好
- Hi. - Hey.
我们能进去吗
Should we come in?
请进
Please.
你好
Hi.
太棒了 这些作品画了多长时间
These are amazing. How long did they take?
它们风格迥异
They're all kind of different, you know?
每一幅作品都经历了
Each one goes through its
自身的死亡与重生
own little process of death and rebirth.
那一幅用了两小时
That one literally took me two hours.
他们都是实实在在的
They're all their own little entities, really.
- 你住这里吗  - 嗯
- You live here, too? - Mm-hmm.
太简陋了
It's so simple.
这无关舒适 你懂吗
It's not about comfort, really, you know?
你多大了
You... How old are you?
十八岁
18.
不会吧
No.
每次我有了灵感
Every time I think about a subject,
甚至去构想一幅自认为应该画的东西
or even try to visualize an image of what I think I should paint,
我觉得自己就像一坨狗屎
I just feel like I'm full of shit,
像我根本不是我自己一样
like I'm trying to be something I'm not.
George 这就是你的本性
George, this is who you are.
这些作品太棒了 真的很棒 很了不起
This stuff is wonderful, man. It really is. It's fantastic.
是吗 只是涂鸦而已 不成形的垃圾
Really? No, they're just doodles, you know, immature crap.
不 哥们 这就是你要作的东西
No, man. This is what you should be painting.
至少你要加入别的东西
At least until you evolve
才能使其完整 知道我的意思吧
into something else, you know what I mean?
但是你得一直练习
But you gotta exercise the muscle
即使你没有什么感觉 知道我的意思吧
even if you're not feeling it, you know what I mean?
你只要 你得实实在在的做 否则它永远不会出现
You just... You gotta do it or else it'll never happen.
哥们 还有
Hey, man, by the way,
干的不错
very nice work.
- 什么  - 干的不错
- Huh? - Very nice work.
这个
Oh.
你俩在一起 是吗
Well, you guys are together, right?
没有
No.
抱歉 那太蠢了 我不该说这些事
I'm sorry. That was stupid. I shouldn't have said anything.
没事 我们不在一起
No, not at all. We're not together.
你喜欢她
You like her.
你应该喜欢她 提个建议
You should like her, if you don't.
我不会打她注意的
I'll leave that alone.
- 太酷了  - 是啊
- That was so cool. - Uh-huh.
他太令人吃惊了 很有天赋 你不觉得吗
I mean, he's amazing. Really talented. Don't you think?
都是些跟风之作 我不确定他是否货真价实
A little derivative. I'm not sure he's the real deal.
是吗 我觉得他就是
Really? He seemed like it to me.
我是说 他是你的导师
I mean, he's a mentor to you now.
- 你不兴奋吗  - 我认为他有点爱吹牛
- Aren't you psyched? - I think he's a bit of a blowhard.
你太怪了
You're so weird.
他提到我没有
Did he say anything about me?
没有
Nope.
- 你看书评了吗  - 嗯
- Did you read the Book Review? - Mmm-hmm.
关于M1主战坦克的新书 令人期待
New book about the M-1 tank. Can't wait.
那你呢
What about you?
我比较喜欢
I'm interested in...
- 作品很棒  - 谢谢
- Great job. - Thank you.
谢谢 我很喜欢它
Thanks. I appreciate it.
谢谢 谢谢 谢谢
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
怎么回事
What happened?
我不想失去这里
I don't wanna lose this!
Viv 我们不会失去这里 我保证
Viv, we're not gonna lose this place. I promise you.
- 我不会相信你  - 他就要成功了
- I don't believe you anymore. - He's gonna come through.
- 不  - 会的 他快成功了
- No! - Yes, he's gonna come through,
而且我还有其他两个孩子
and I have two other guys...
总是其他人 总是其他东西
It's always some other person, it's always some other thing.
我厌倦了这些
I'm tired of this!
嘿
Hey!
- 怎么了  - 没什么
- What? - Nothing.
你还好吧
You okay?
我对激素过敏
I'm allergic to hormones.
什么激素
What hormones?
自己的
Mine.
- 你好 George  - Zoe 好地方
- Hi, George! - Hey, Zoe. Great place.
你家人去赈济处吃饭了么
Your folks getting dinner at the soup kitchen?
不 他们不住这里 住在格林威治
No, they don't live here. They live in Greenwich.
- 你一个人住这里吗  - 是啊 George
- You live here alone? - Yes, George.
我要去市里上学
I wanted to go to school in the city,
所以父母给我租了这里
so my parents rented me this place.
好啊 Nick
Hey, Nick.
很火辣啊 Sal
Looking pretty hot, Sal.
谢谢
Thanks.
我想我们需要单独相处 就你和我
I think we need some one-on-one time, you and me.
真的吗
Oh, you do, do you?
Zinavoy 怎么穿着外套
Zinavoy, what's with the overcoat?
我们在室内
We're indoors now.
我喜欢层次感
I like layers.
- 哥们 看到没  - 什么
- Did you see it, man? - See what?
邀请帖 看看
The invite. Check it out.
给力
Bang!
很有立体感 是吗
It's pretty solid, huh?
好吧 各位 让我们摇吧去
All right, y'all. Let's go to the club.
我穿成这样没预想要来吧
I'm not dressed for this.
挺好的 大家都差不多
You're fine. And we're with Will.
没啥大不了 但我从没参加过这种活动
It's not a big deal, but I've never been to one of these before.
别担心 丢不了你
Don't worry. I won't lose you.
- 嘿  - 嘿 伙计们
- Hey! - Hey, guys.
给你的 你的服饰 拿着它
This is yours, for the drawing. Dominate it.
谢谢
Thanks.
来吧
Come on!
来呀
Come on.
- Nick在这里  - 嘿
- Nick is here! - Hey!
抱歉
Sorry.
嗨
Hi.
要我给你介绍几个女孩吗
Do you want me to introduce you to any girls?
什么
What?
我有很多荡妇会合你的口味
I have a lot of slutty friends here you might like.
不 不 我还好
Oh, no. No, I'm cool.
我是说 我只摇吧就挺好
I mean, I'm cool just hanging out.
那好吧 George 我们都知道你在等谁
That's all right, George. We all know who you're waiting for.
什么 不 我没有
What? No. I'm not.
- Zoe 我没有  - 拜拜
- Zoe, that's not what I... - Bye-bye!
耶 耶
Yeah, yeah!
10 9 8 7 6 5
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six, five,
4 3 2 1
four, three, two, one!
新年快乐
Happy New Year!
嘿
Hey.
你怎么不和Nick在一起
Why didn't you go with Nick?
为什么要和他一起 我在那找了你两个小时
Why would I? I spent two hours in there looking for you.
- 你和他约会过吗  - 只持续了5分钟
- Didn't you used to date him? - Yeah, for like five minutes.
你为什么喜欢他
Why do you like that guy?
我没有 我要是喜欢就告诉你了
I don't! I would tell you if I did.
对不起
I'm so sorry.
Sally 对不起 我搞砸了你的欢乐之夜
Sally, I'm so sorry. I ruined your night.
应该是我道歉 我把你晾在一旁
No, I'm sorry. I lost you.
食言了
Broke my promise.
我觉得你
I think you're
了不起
amazing.
这个说法真烂
What a stupid thing to say.
不 不 这很
No. No, it was...
很贴心
It was sweet.
来吧
Come on.
小心
Careful.
这是终极解药
This is the cure to end all cures.
我爸经常放个生鸡蛋更有效果
My daddy used to put a raw egg in his to really get the effects.
- 你要加蛋吗  - 不用了
- You want an egg? - No.
这是醒酒液
You've heard of a hair of the dog?
上面是牛肉汤
Beef bouillon floater there.
感觉怎么样
How are you feeling?
好多了 谢谢你照顾我
Much better. Thank you for taking care of me.
妈妈 你在做什么
Mom, what are you doing?
你得滋补一下嘛 坏脾气小姐
But you have to have a coalminer's tonic, Miss Grumpy.
就像疫苗一样
It's like a vaccine.
我不管了 我回房间
I can't deal. I'm going back to bed.
她起床比斗牛犬还凶
Angrier than a pit bull when she wakes up.
我喜欢这个孩子
I like that boy.
我也是
So do I.
Sal 我认为你不能在他身上浪费时间了
Sal, I don't think you should be messing around with him.
你是在给我约会建议吗
Are you giving me dating advice?
我只是认为你应该和适合自己的对象约会
I just think you should be going out with someone your own speed.
别担心 我们只是朋友
Don't worry, we're just friends.
这才是我担心的
That's exactly what worries me.
Charlotte 我不评论你的社交生活
Charlotte, I don't comment on your social life.
你也无权评论我的
You hardly have the right to comment on mine.
- 我看到了他看你的眼神  - 天呐
- I've seen the way he looks at you. - Jesus.
他对此的感觉没那么简单
This all means something much more to him.
相信我 我一辈子都在游戏感情
Trust me, I've played with their affections my whole life.
但面对真感情 就不能玩了
But with the good ones, it's not right.
那是你的做法 我和你不一样
That's what you do. It's not what I'm doing.
这个创意不错
This is a great idea, by the way.
几个月后我有一个画展
I got a show coming up in a couple of months.
我需要一些灵感 知道吧
I needed some inspiration, you know?
一流的作品
Big time.
你喜欢这个吗
Do you like this?
我理解它 你呢
I get it. Do you?
我认为任何人都可以
I think anyone could turn this out,
但是为何想要理解它
except why would they want to?
它说明了什么
What's it saying?
使空间看起来更大 知道吗
Makes a room look great, though, you know?
看上去像钱
It looks like money.
上帝
Oh, God.
这对我来说就像天堂
This is heaven to me.
确实很棒
Pretty great.
它让你立马感受到某些东西 你知道我的意思吧
This makes you feel something instantly, you know what I mean?
比如生气
Like anger
或者愤怒
or wrath.
性欲
Lust.
你和Sally怎么样了 有进展不
So, how's it going with our friend Sally? Make any moves?
她对我不感兴趣
She hasn't shown any interest.
那你呢
Well, have you?
你是怎么想的
What do you think, she's
她会满世界的说爱你吗
gonna go around wearing a sign around her neck?
女人喜欢被追求
Women love being desired.
你只需把她推到墙上 然后吻她
You just go throw her up against the wall, start kissing her.
她回吻说明有戏
Chances are she'll kiss you back.
如果没有 至少你尝试过
And if she doesn't, then at least you tried.
你得跨出一步 否则你会失去她
You gotta do something or you might lose her.
你喜欢这个
You love this.
这个不错
No, it's good.
迷恋客观事物 挺适合你的
Fetishizing an object. That suits you.
难以置信我们也会随大流
I can't believe we're participating in this consumer circle jerk.
单身者今晚需要紧紧相随
The dateless need to stick together tonight.
像幸存者一样相拥取暖
We're like survivors huddling for warmth.
你一定过了好几次情人节
You've probably had so many Valentines.
这是委婉的说我水性杨花吗
Is that some kind of euphemism for slut?
印象最深的是和我爸爸
The one I remember most was my dad.
在哪
Where was that?
离开田纳西州之前
It was before we left Tennessee.
我6岁 他已经走了
I was six and he had already left,
但是他经常回来
but he'd come back every so often.
他骑着摩托载着我呼啸而过
He roared up on his motorcycle, took me out alone.
晚饭时用薄饼蘸着巧克力糖浆
We had pancakes with chocolate syrup at a diner, at night.
他都让我点餐
He let me order.
你爸爸在哪
Where's your father?
在北京 他几年前为了挣钱去的
Beijing. He moved there years ago for the economic boom.
你们联系过吗
You guys have a relationship?
他填支票 支付我的学费
He checks in, pays my tuition.
但是我们之间差别太大
But we couldn't be more different.
我认为他有点失望
I think he's a little disappointed.
我7岁时和他在东京待过一段时间
I spent some time in Tokyo with him when I was seven.
他在那里经营公司 每天工作12 14小时
He was running a company there, working 12, 14 hours a day.
所以我有了一个
So, I had this full-time
不会说英语的全职保姆
Japanese babysitter who didn't speak English.
我们根本不能理解对方
We couldn't understand each other at all.
很快 她厌倦了照顾我
Pretty soon, she ran out of things to do with me
而她也不许我离开酒店
and I ended up never leaving the hotel room.
我就像一头小牛
I was like a veal.
你小时候什么样
What were you like as a child?
比我现在好多了
I was such a better person than I am now.
- 得了吧  - 没开玩笑
- Come on. - I'm serious.
我快乐 开放 好奇
I was happy, I was open, I was curious.
但我告诉你 我知道何时会结束
But I'll tell you this, I knew when it was ending.
当我意识到我要改变
I was overwhelmed with
意识到这比看上去还糟糕
sadness when I realized that I was gonna change
被悲伤击垮的时候就会结束了
and that it was all most likely gonna get worse.
比如现在的思乡之情 我无法摆脱它
Like a nostalgia for the present, I couldn't shake it.
什么
What?
我很奇怪 对吧
I'm weird, right?
不
No.
你不奇怪
No, you're not.
奇怪的是我这么久
It's weird not having a boyfriend.
都没有男朋友
It's been so long.
因为你都高三了
That's because it's the
都是些比你小的师弟
first year at school nobody's older than you.
资源稀缺啊
Your pool dried up.
- 你怎么知道 －我是一个细心的人
- How do you know that? - I'm a very insightful person.
你做过么
Have you ever had sex?
当然 很多
Yeah, tons.
说真的 有过吗
No, really. Have you?
你为什么这么问
Why are you asking me this?
你知道我没有过
You know I haven't.
哦 我不知道 我只是有点好奇
Well, I don't know, I'm just wondering.
你是否想过和我
Have you ever thought about me?
什么意思
What do you mean?
你知道我在说什么 你有没有想过和我
You know what I mean. Have you ever thought about it?
你说这些干嘛
Why are you doing this?
你会和我上床么
Will you have sex with me?
开个玩笑啦
I'm just kidding.
糟糕的主意
Bad idea.
那样也太怪了
I mean, can you imagine how weird that would be?
你是我唯一的知心朋友
You're my only real friend.
不能毁了这段友情
Let's not ruin it.
我们是不是该找Will和Zoe一起开房
Should we check in with Will and Zoe?
George?
我得走了
I have to go.
什么
What?
我不舒服
I'm not feeling well.
好吧 那我们明天见
Okay. Well, will I see you tomorrow?
不清楚
I don't know.
这个是不对的 它只是玩笑
This is wrong. It's a joke.
George 你想多了
You think too much, George!
出去
Get out.
George 你怎么回事 为什么你不在学校
George? What is going on? Why aren't you at school?
我在家当然就
If you speak even the most
不在学校了
rudimentary form of the English language,
这么简单的逻辑都不懂
then you'll understand this,
让我自己待会
leave me alone.
你刚才和我说什么
What did you just say to me?
Vivian 我说得很清楚
Vivian, my voice is calm.
我现在是一个游离的思考个体
I'm a free-thinking individual
不参与你的话题
who chooses not to be engaged in this discussion.
请离开
Please.
George 你在做什么
George, what are you doing?
Jack 对不起 我现在需要自己呆会
I'm sorry, Jack. I need to be left alone right now.
你的功课怎么样
What about your work?
我现在不想做
I just can't do it right now.
我现在正痛苦呢
I'm going through something.
真可悲
That's pathetic.
但至少是事实
At least it's the truth.
那是什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
- 你好 － 你好
- Hey. - Hey.
- 你怎么样 － 很好
- How are you? - Good.
不错
That's good.
一切  一切都好么
Everything... Everything all right?
没错 挺好  一切都好
Yeah. Yeah, everything's all right.
George 怎么样 他没有回我的电话
How's George? He hasn't returned my calls.
对 这正是我要和你讨论的
Yeah, that's kind of what I wanted to talk to you about.
他也不和我说话
He's not exactly speaking to me either.
- 为什么 发生了什么 - 我也不知道
- Why? What happened? - I don't know.
你知道George
You know George.
我想 他是比较难懂的
He's complicated, I guess.
嗯
Yeah.
我好奇
I was wondering,
对你而言 我不止是George的朋友吧
I'm not just George's friend to you, am I?
Sally 你和George应该在一起
You and George should be together, Sally.
我们只是朋友
We're just friends.
不可能
There's no such thing.
我喜欢这首曲子
I love this song.
跳舞吧
You wanna dance?
来吧
Come on.
怎么
What?
我们不应该这样
We shouldn't be doing this.
- 我们只是跳舞 - 是么
- We're just dancing. - Oh, yeah?
George.
我一直等你的论文呢
Been looking forward to
今天最后一天了
reading your Hardy paper. Today's the day.
对不起 我还没有做
Sorry, I don't have it.
George 这是你的毕业论文
George, this was your final project of the year.
交论文 然后年终考试 我多么希望你能毕业
After this, there's just exams. How am I supposed to grade you?
我保证 我下周交
I'll have it to you by next week, I promise.
那似乎不行
That's not gonna be good enough.
Pal 你好
Hey, pal.
我召集这个会议是因为你的老师们反映
I called this meeting because your teachers have reported to me
你还是不做作业
that you continue to refuse to do the course work.
你一点都不努力
You have made zero effort
在摩根学校这里虚度光阴
to turn your career here at Morgan around.
是 没错
Yes, I did.
我是说 最初我也努力过
I mean, I did struggle
但是我没有做到
with it at the beginning, but I just couldn't.
好 你没有时间了
Well, you are out of time.
决定你未来的时刻已经到了
The moment to decide your future has arrived.
现在 根据这些老师们的建议
Now, against the recommendation of some in this room,
我让你自己选择
I'm giving you a choice.
第一开除
First is expulsion.
如果这是你想要的
It's yours if you want it.
第二选择
Second option,
如果你想毕业
if you want to graduate,
你补齐所有你落下的作业
you make up every single assignment you missed.
所有的论文 练习
Every paper, every exercise.
也就是说相当一年的作业
Essentially, a year's worth of homework.
漏了一个 就没有毕业证书
If even one is missing on graduation day, no diploma.
你还有3周多一点的时间
You have a little over three weeks.
George 我过去坚信
George, I used to believe
你比其他人有潜力
you had more potential than anyone else here.
但你从没证明给我看 哪怕一次也没
But you never delivered, not once.
我以前从来都不浪费时间对你发火
I wasn't gonna waste the time getting mad at you.
现在我也不想浪费时间维护你
I'm not gonna waste the time defending you now.
暂不提你对老师的不尊重 George
Forget the lack of respect you show, George.
这就是度过我们的人生的方式
This is the way we make our living, how we spend our lives.
但是你从来不关心这里发生的一切
But you simply don't care what goes on around here.
为什么我们还要以德报怨
Why would we continue to reward that?
你是对的
You're right.
我不该这样对你们
You shouldn't reward it.
我真的不知道该说什么
I honestly don't know what to say.
也许应该退学
Maybe it should be expulsion.
你还是下周一告诉我们
Let us know on Monday.
好 行
All right. All right.
谢谢
Thank you.
你们告知我的父母没
Did you tell my parents about this?
是 George 必须的
Yes, George, I had to.
嘿
Hey.
我不知道该说什么
I don't know what to say.
是我的错  我一直忙着
Is it my fault? I mean, I've had a lot on my mind and...
不是你的错
It's not your fault.
我认为我做不到
I don't think I can do it.
哦 什么意思 不是还有另外一种选择
Well, what do you mean? What other choice is there?
妈妈 我不确信我能做到
Mom, I'm not sure that I can.
你不得不去做
You're just gonna have to do it.
你应该坐下然后去完成
You're just gonna have to sit down and just do it!
妈妈 我尝试坦诚的和你说
Mom, I'm trying to speak to you honestly.
我不在乎 我已经受够了你的谎言
I don't care! I'm done listening to your lies!
拜托 这事不可能办得到的
Come on, that's really the way to fix this!
George 这是你的问题 你闯的祸
Hey, George! This is your mess, and it's a disaster.
Jack 你说的对 是我的事
You're right, Jack. It is my mess.
我解决我的问题 你处理好你自己的
I'll handle my mess, you handle yours.
- 行 注意你的口气  - 等等 Viv
- Okay, watch that tone. - Wait, Viv.
什么意思
What does that mean?
我是说 你想告诉我们
I mean, you wanna tell us where you've been spending your days
你这个冬天这些天在哪里度过的
for a couple of months this past winter?
你的问题处理得怎么样了
What's going on with your disaster?
电话断了 我们支付不起电费
Phone gets shut off. We can't pay the electricity.
家具一个个逐渐在消失
Furniture is disappearing around here piece by piece.
George 住口 你不明白
George, stop it. You don't understand.
那你呢
Do you?
那你知道Jack 这几周都在街上流浪
Do you know that Jack was wandering the streets for weeks,
假装去上班
pretending to go to work?
Jack 你解决这个问题了么
Did you get that sorted out, Jack?
或者像一个无家可归的人在
Or are you still working out
咖啡店想办法
of a coffee shop booth like a homeless person?
Jack 住手
Jack, stop!
别打了
Stop it!
Jack 住手
Jack! Stop!
放开我
Get off!
George!
Sally!
Sally?
George!
怎么啦 怎么了
What's going on? What happened?
怎么回事
What's wrong?
为什么
What is it?
George.
嘿 George
George, hey.
我只是想确认你是否还好
I just wanted to make sure you're all right.
George 我真的也不好过
I had a really hard time, George.
我发誓 我保证 我
I swear. I promise, I...
我以为你说不会打她主意
I thought you were gonna leave it alone.
我不是要说对不起
I'm not gonna say sorry.
是我不会更好么
Isn't it better that it's me?
相比那些他刚认识的惹人厌的家伙
As opposed to some douche bag she just met
这样你还不能正视她么
and wouldn't even let you look at her?
你还想我说谢谢嘛
You want me to thank you?
我的确对她有感觉
I actually felt something.
这个并不总是发生
That doesn't always happen.
已经很久没有这样的感觉了
It hasn't happened in a very long time.
我已经等的够久了
And I've lived long enough
我知道我应该立刻行动
to know that when it does, you should act on it.
我认为你没有准备好
I didn't think you were ready.
我曾经认为你很酷
I thought you were so cool.
我从来没有遇到这么酷的人
I never meet anyone cool.
嗨
Hi.
我不想呆在那里
I didn't want to be up there.
那里是不太好呆
Can't have been fun for you.
他摔断了锁骨 我们一整夜都在急症室
He broke his collarbone. We were in the ER all night.
我很抱歉 这本不该发生的
I'm so sorry. That should have never happened.
妈妈 是我先挑起的
Mom, I started it.
他可都50岁了
He's a 50-year-old man.
他应该保护你的
He's supposed to protect you.
妈妈 是我的错 我很无礼
Mom, I'm obnoxious, I'm deeply disrespectful.
我们要离婚
We're getting a divorce.
不必如此 我确定他不会再这样了
Come on, I'm sure he'll never do it again.
既然他知道我能弄到他住院
Now that he knows I can hospitalize him.
我们早就走到那一步了
We were already headed there.
一年前他做生意破产了
His business went bankrupt about a year ago,
我想我应该相信他 支持他
and I thought I should have faith in him and support him.
但是他总是找借口
But there was always some sort of excuse,
总是说他会时来运转的
or his luck was about to turn.
然后说服我把房子做抵押
So, he convinced me to mortgage the apartment,
再然后是我的生意
and then my own business.
但总是不够
But it was never enough.
他就是个混蛋 我早该告诉你的
He's a sick man, and I should have told you,
但是你压力太大
but you were under enough
我不想再让你心烦意乱了
pressure and I didn't wanna distract you.
心烦意乱也不错
I like distractions.
现在更严重了
It gets worse.
我得把房子卖了
I have to sell the apartment.
你说什么
What?
我的信用卡再也支撑不起这些债务了
The debt has erased my credit.
我该怎么办
What am I gonna do?
我答应了
I'll do it.
别挂机
Hold on.
你只有三周时间了
You have three weeks.
而且你还得上学 还要期末考
And you still have to come to school and take finals.
知道了没
You know that already?
找你老师要以往的作业
Pick up your assignment packets
少了一份 休想拿到毕业证
from your teachers. You miss one, no diploma.
- 知道了 - 出去吧
- Okay. - Go.
我考虑了很久 George
I've given this a lot of thought, George.
我不认为我会宽容你
I don't think I'm being easy on you.
我也不相信那些沉闷无趣的作业
I simply don't believe that dull, lifeless assignments
可以用来衡量一个人的灵魂
are the measures of a person's soul.
我只要一张
I want one,
有意义的画作
one meaningful work from you.
我要你审视自我 倾听心声
I want you to look in the mirror, listen to your gut,
与真实的自己对话
and make an image that speaks to the real you.
你在乎什么 相信什么
What you care about. What you believe.
可高山 可流水
It can be big, it can be small.
就算画得再糟糕
It can be painted in bat shit.
只要真诚无惧就可以
As long as it's honest and fearless.
Harris 你的帮助我实在是无以为报
Harris, you have no idea how much this helps...
停 停 以免你误会
But! But. The caveat.
假若我觉得不对头
If I smell a rat,
你还是没能找到
if you didn't find something
你一直没有勇气说的东西
you've never had the courage to say before,
我是不会让你过的 你绝对毕不了业
I don't pass you. You don't get out of here.
你的前途将化作乌有
All your work down the drain.
走吧 快 现在可以走了
Now, go, get out of here.
你还好吧
How are you?
你和Jack没啥事吧
How are things with Jack?
真搞不懂 我和Dustin交往有什么问题吗
Look, what is so wrong with me seeing Dustin?
他告诉我他不会管的
He told me he was gonna leave it alone.
但是你和他说我们没在一起
But you told him we weren't together!
那你指望我说什么
What should I have said?
问题是你想说什么
What did you wanna say?
你又来了 心理游戏总是玩不够
There you go again with the mind games.
背弃信用 残酷成性的贱妇
Treacherous, sadistic little hussy.
George 我们之间没什么
George! There was nothing between us.
- 我很抱歉 - 不 你说得对
- I'm sorry. - No. You're right.
我得走了 我要是不把这一年
I gotta go. I have to make up
堆积的家庭作业补完 就别想毕业了
a year's worth of homework or I don't graduate.
- 什么 - 祝你和Dustin幸福愉快
- What? - Have fun with Dustin.
介绍你俩认识我真是开心
I'm so pleased to have made the introduction.
这里很不错
And it's good.
我们在这里有过几许美好回忆
We've had some great memories here, you know?
我们最好快点把这地方租下来
We should definitely look into signing a lease for this place.
- 这太完美了 - 当然 当然
- It's absolutely perfect. - Sure, sure.
这间房不错 宝贝
It's a great room. Hi, honey.
我把房子卖了
I think I'm done.
我作业也完成了
Me, too.
我们一家人从前过得很快乐
We had a lot of fun in the beginning, you, me, and your father.
我也不知道为什么会变成这样
I don't get what happened.
自从爸爸那事之后
After Dad.
物换星移
Things change.
有时候你甚至觉察不到变化
Sometimes so quickly you don't even notice it.
也许吧 幸福
I don't know. Happiness is,
就像你必须照顾好的东西
like, something you have to look after,
要小心翼翼
be vigilant about.
你知道Jack是爱我们的
I mean, you know that Jack loved us.
这不是什么黄粱美梦
That wasn't an illusion.
他把你当作儿子般疼爱
He loved you like a son.
你知道他现在在哪里吗
Do you know where he is now?
不知道
No.
对以后的人生有什么想法没
Do you have any idea of what you wanna do?
我想去读艺校
I wanna try and get into an art school.
我需要专业的训练
I need real training.
谢谢你能来
Thank you for coming.
一波未平一波又起 我心乱如麻
So much has happened, and so much is happening, and...
我需要你这个朋友 好吗
I just need you to be my friend, okay?
我真的 真的很需要你 求求你了
I really, really need that. Please.
我妈妈要嫁给一个才认识三个月的人
My mom is marrying this guy she's known for three months
还要搬去德州和他住一起
and moving to Texas to be with him.
她已经走了
She's already down there.
结婚了 意味着她不能收赡养费了
Getting engaged means her alimony payment stops,
也不能供我下年去Boulder读书了
which means she can't pay my tuition for Boulder next year,
这相当于是说我出不去了
which means I don't get out.
她想让我跟她一起搬去德州
She wants me to go live with her in Texas.
那你去吗
What are you gonna do?
这很难决定
That's the hard part.
因为我明天就要走了
Because I'm leaving tomorrow.
要去哪
Where are you going?
我和Dustin打算夏日背包游欧洲
Dustin and I are gonna backpack around Europe for the summer.
他作品卖出去了 把这送我当礼物
His show sold out. It's his present to me.
那毕业典礼怎么办
What about graduation?
经历了这么多 我受够了 毕业证书就让他们寄给我吧
After everything, I'm over it. They can mail it to me.
那Zoe和Will他们呢
And Zoe, Will, and...
我很喜欢这些家伙
I love those guys,
但那都不是真实的我
but that was never really me.
那游完欧洲之后呢
And after Europe?
天知道 反正不会是德州
Who knows? Not Texas.
我必须告诉你些东西
I need to tell you something.
你说得对 某种程度上讲
You were right, in a way.
我不该把话憋着不说的
I should've been able to say what I wanted to.
我爱上你了 已经很久很久了
I'm in love with you. I always have been.
我认为是你待我不公平
I thought you were the unfair one,
但是于我而言我也没说
but it was unfair of me not to say it.
所以 我就这么说了
So, I've said it.
我一无是处
I was nothing.
我感觉自己一无是处
I felt like nothing.
但是
Less than.
你改变了我
You changed that.
你知道我们终有一天会在一起
You know we're gonna be together one day.
我们都必须把身上的糟糕处境解决掉
We have to sort through all of our messed-up issues
而你也只能
and you have to sleep with
多和几个女孩深交才能一吐为快
a lot of girls to get it out of your system.
别走
Don't go.
算我求你
Please.
人生很长
It's a long life.
我们并不孤身一人
We're not done.
背信弃言 残酷成性的贱货
Treacherous, sadistic little hussy.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
都在这了
Here it is.
我们会好好看的
We'll see.
我们就到此为止吧
We are getting down to the wire.
我也许会喊你名字 又也许不会
I'll either be calling your name or I won't.
你他妈的好样的
Son of a bitch.
Mara Ryder 你今天顺利毕业了
Mara Ryder.
她有说她什么时候回来吗
Did she say when she'd be back?
真不敢相信她甚至连电话也不打给我
I can't believe she didn't even call me.
我做错什么了
What did I do?
Will Sharpe 你今天顺利毕业了
Will Sharpe.
他们就要关门了
They're about to close the doors.
达拉斯航机2013号最后登机通告
Final boarding call for Dallas Flight 2013,
乘客Diana Mayer请速登机
passenger Diana Mayer.
来这里
Come here.
Veronica Walsh 你今天顺利毕业了
Veronica Walsh.
你会没事的
You're gonna be okay.
我知道
I'm fine.
我保证大把女孩子排着队追你呢
We'll have plenty of girls lined up for you, I promise.
Zoe 说真的 我
Zoe, really, I'm...
谢谢你
Thank you.
还有
And
George Zinavoy 你今天顺利毕业了
George Zinavoy.
一切皆有可能
Anything is possible.
- 嘿 - 嘿 什么事
- Hey. - Hey, what's up?
我都饿坏了
I'm starving.
还不错嘛
Not bad.
我是说还可以
I mean, it's all right.
挺不错
It's good.
那你打算怎样
So, what are you gonna do?
要留下来吗
Are you staying?
我也不知道
I don't know.
? Trav'ling lady, stay awhile ?
? I'm just a station on your way ?
? I know I'm not your lover ?
? Trav'ling lady, stay awhile ?
? Until the night is over ?
And why are you so quiet now ?
? standing there in the doorway? ?
? You chose your journey long before ?
? You came upon this highway ?
? Trav'ling lady, stay awhile ?
? Until the night is over ?
? What the rest did I was average ?
? But I don't mind ?
? Drawn on two sides without disguise ?
? And you, you don't believe me ?
? And I, I find it easy ?
? Easy ?
? You're recruited head diluted through a glass eye ?
? Dreams in fiction lost religion ?
? But I don't mind ?
? Cause I spit fire on lovers and liars ?
? And you, you don't believe me ?
? And I, I find it easy ?
? Easy ?
? And I, I spit fire on lovers and liars ?
? And you, you don't believe me ?
? And I, I find it easy ?
? Easy ?
? I, I spit fire on lovers and liars ?
? And you won't deceive me ?
? And I, I find it easy ?
? Easy ?
? The hours of choking century ?
? I blame you ?
? I thank you ?
? Wasn't fit to have you But I will never run and hide ?
? I don't feel so bad And then I will not apologize ?
? I am fit to hang and in the falling rain ?
? And I meant to make it out tonight ?
? The hours that go in front of me ?
? Remind it how it used be ?
? And you down in the grass with me ?
? The hours of choking century ?
? I blame you ?
? I thank you ?
? I thank you?
? Yeah, you come to mind ?
? Yeah, you come to mind?